[
  {
    "name": "Book City",
    "id": "history",
    "theme": "blue",
    "action": "360",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "The first words spoken on the moon by Buzz Aldrin were these:",
        "start": "Contact ",
        "answer": "Light"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "What U.S. President committed an unpardonable sin by kissing the Queen Mother on the lips?",
        "options": [
          "George W. Bush",
          "Jimmy Carter",
          "Barack Obama",
          "Lyndon B. Johnson",
          "Ronald Reagan"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Cleopatra was Egyptian.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "The Rosetta Stone is the name of the limestone slab that became the key for deciphering ancient Egyptian hieroglyphics.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Prior to 1664 New York was called:",
        "start": "New ",
        "answer": "Amsterdam"
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "What are the surnames of Bonnie and Clyde?",
        "options": [
          "Parson",
          "Parker",
          "Patterson",
          "Barlow",
          "Barret",
          "Barrow"
        ],
        "answer": [
          1,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Joan of Arc, in the 15th century, was the first female promoted to this rank in the French army:",
        "options": [
          "Lieutenant",
          "Sergeant",
          "General",
          "Captain"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "In which year did William Shakespeare die?",
        "min": 1615,
        "max": 1635,
        "answer": 1616
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "On which island was Napoleon born?",
        "options": [
          "Sardinia",
          "Corsica",
          "Tahiti",
          "Réunion",
          "New Caledonia"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which states did the United States gain after the Mexican War?",
        "options": [
          "Arizona",
          "New Mexico",
          "Louisiana",
          "California",
          "Nevada",
          "Utah",
          "Texas"
        ],
        "answer": [
          1,
          3,
          6
        ]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },

  {
    "name": "Sports",
    "id": "sports",
    "theme": "purple",
    "action": "cardboard",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What is the national sport of Canada?",
        "answer": "Lacrosse"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Which country won every Olympic Men’s hockey gold medal from 1928 to 1956?",
        "options": [
          "Canada",
          "Russia",
          "India",
          "USA"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "A biathlon event consists of running a half marathon and biking 56 miles.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many players are in a game of water polo?",
        "min": 10,
        "max": 25,
        "answer": 14
      },
      {
        "type": "toggle-translate",
        "question": "Which sports and team names are incorrectly associated?",
        "options": [
          [
            "Cleveland Indians",
            "Baseball"
          ],
          [
            "Leicester Tigers",
            "Rugby Union"
          ],
          [
            "Bradford Bulls",
            "Hockey"
          ],
          [
            "Belle Vue Aces",
            "Poker"
          ],
          [
            "Wigan Wasps",
            "Lacrosse"
          ],
          [
            "Kent Spitfires",
            "Cricket"
          ]
        ],
        "answer": [
          2,
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which cities have hosted the Olympic games?",
        "options": [
          "Athens",
          "Lake Placid",
          "Innsbruck",
          "New York",
          "Capetown",
          "St. Mortiz"
        ],
        "answer": [
          0,
          1,
          2,
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Which American was the best paid sportsman in 1920?",
        "options": [
          "Jack Dempsey",
          "Babe Ruth",
          "Big Bill Tilden",
          "Bobby Jones"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": " What do you call a stadium used for cycling events?",
        "options": [
          "Cycleplex",
          "Velodrome",
          "Pumptrack",
          "Speedway"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "In 1954, Joe Di Maggio married Norma Jean Baker who was also known as?",
        "answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "About how many kilometers are in a marathon?",
        "min": 10,
        "max": 65,
        "answer": 42
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Spellcast Game",
    "id": "food",
    "theme": "green",
    "action": "game",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Name the Italian, semi-soft, rich cheese with blue veins through it.",
        "options": [
          "Ricotta",
          "Blue Cheese",
          "Gorgonzola",
          "Parmesan"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Coffee beans contain more caffeine than tea leaves.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "What are the three ingredients in mead (spices excluded)?",
        "options": [
          "Sugar",
          "Honey",
          "Cinnamon",
          "Water",
          "Brown Sugar",
          "Yeast",
          "Salt"
        ],
        "answer": [
          1,
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What crop does the Colorado Beetle attack?",
        "options": [
          "Corn",
          "Garlic",
          "Potato",
          "Wheat"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "What vegetable did Mark Twain describe as “cabbage with a college education”?",
        "options": [
          "Spinach",
          "Broccoli",
          "Cauliflower",
          "Kale"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What name is given to a sugar syrup which is gently heated until it browns?",
        "answer": "Caramel"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "In Which city was chop suey invented?",
        "options": [
          "Hong Kong",
          "Taipei",
          "New York",
          "San Francisco"
        ],
        "answer": [3]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
        "min": 1,
        "max": 10,
        "answer": 9
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "In which American State did chili con carne originate?",
        "answer": "Texas"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What is the correct name for a cluster or bunch of bananas?",
        "options": [
          "Foot",
          "Hand",
          "Flock",
          "Pod"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Starcast Game",
    "id": "entertainment",
    "theme": "red",
    "action": "game",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Where was superman born?",
        "answer": "Krypton"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What catchphrase is associated with the Daleks from Doctor Who?",
        "options": [
          "Eradicate",
          "Exterminate",
          "Eliminate",
          "Execute"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "In the film Cool Hand Luke, how many hard boiled eggs did Paul Newman eat to win a bet?",
        "min": 20,
        "max": 80,
        "answer": 50
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Frank Sinatra paid a $240,000 ransom to free his kidnapped son.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which two British actors have played Obi Wan Kenobi in the Star Wars films?",
        "options": [
          "Sir Alec Guinness",
          "David Prowse",
          "James Earl Jones",
          "Harrison Ford",
          "Ewan McGregor",
          "Anthony Daniels"
        ],
        "answer": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many Oscars were won by the film Matrix at the 2000 Academy Awards ceremony?",
        "min": 0,
        "max": 11,
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Late American artist Andy Warhol observed:",
        "start": "“Two people kissing always looks like ",
        "end": ".”",
        "answer": "Fish"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Who played Dr. John Hammond in Jurassic Park?",
        "options": [
          "Anthony Hopkins",
          "Jeff Goldblum",
          "Richard Attenborough",
          "Emmet Brown"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "What year did the Live Aid concerts take place?",
        "min": 1965,
        "max": 1990,
        "answer": 1985
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What is Mr. Burns’ first name?",
        "answer": "Charles"
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  }
]
